So, no, this policy is not designed to...
I thought when I said it was a dumb question, it meant no.
Well, I just want to be clear and precise.
I appreciate you trying to qualify my questions,
but nevertheless, I think it's a fair one that a lot of people have.
My full answer is no, that is a lie, and it's a dumb question.
But you said something else baked into the premise of one of your questions.
You said, well, aren't we provoking...
Illinois governor says we're provoking actions that are unlawful.
Why would the mere presence...
Just think about this for a second.
If I put federal law enforcement and National Guard into a nice, sleepy southern town...